		 <ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeIntro"  >Take the Plunge</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeOverviewShort"  >
Obtain 10 different marine animal species to transform a small zoo into a bustling, beautiful marine park. Complete all the scenarios in this campaign to unlock the Blue Whale Hall!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeOverview"  >
      The owners of a small local zoo want to expand it by adding aquatic exhibits. They hired you to help them take the plunge into the exciting world of marine animals.
         <p/>
         The owners' long-term goal is to acquire 10 different marine animal species. To start, they want you to acquire three different species of marine animal.
        <p/>
        (Tip: All new animals in Zoo Tycoon 2: Marine Mania count as marine animals, but a few others, such as the polar bear, also count. Any animal species with tank walls listed in its zookeeper recommendations qualifies as a marine animal for this scenario.)      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeSix"  >
      The owners are so thrilled you obtained your first three marine animal species that they gave you a free seahorse bouncy ride! You can find it crated near the zoo's entrance.
      <p/>
      The owners set a new goal for you to display six or more marine species in your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeTen"  >
      The zoo now features six different species of marine animal. The owners are so happy with your work that they gave you a free marine gift cart. You can find it crated near the zoo's entrance.
      <p/>
      To establish the zoo's reputation as a marine attraction, the owners want you to obtain four more marine animal species. Remember, display a total of 10 different species of marine animal to win the scenario!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeSuccessOverview"  >
      The owners are ecstatic about the success of the zoo. You proved yourself capable of caring for many different marine species. Outstanding work!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeGuest1Overview"  >Since you did such a great job, the owners are eager for you to attract more guests. To encourage your success, they promise to give you $10,000 after 50 guests visit the zoo.     
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeGuest1Success"  >More than 50 guests visited your zoo, and as promised, the owners gave you $10,000! Next, they promise to give you $20,000 if you attract a grand total of 100 guests to the zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeGuest2Success"  >Your zoo attracted more than 100 guests! The zoo owners rewarded you a $20,000 cash grant. To sweeten the deal, the owners promise to pay you $30,000 if you attract a grand total of 150 guests.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeGuest3Success"  >Over the months, more than 150 guests visited your zoo! The zoo owners rewarded your excellent work with a $30,000 cash grant.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeOverallGoal"  >Obtain 10 different marine animal species for your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeThreeGoal"  >Display three or more different species of marine animal in the zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeThreeGoalDone"  >You have three or more marine species on display!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeSixGoal"  >Display six or more different species in the zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeSixGoalDone"  >You have six or more different species on display!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeTenGoal"  >Display 10 or more different species in the zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeTenGoalDone"  >You have 10 or more different species on display!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeGuestGoal1"  >Attract a grand total of 50 guests to your zoo to receive a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeGuestGoal1Done"  >You received a cash grant after 50 guests visited your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeGuestGoal2"  >Attract a grand total of 100 guests to your zoo to receive a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeGuestGoal2Done"  >You received a cash grant after 100 guests visited your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeGuestGoal3"  >Attract a grand total of 150 guests to your zoo to receive a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:TakeThePlungeGuestGoal3Done"  >You received a cash grant after 150 guests visited your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesIntro"  >The Oceans' Biomes</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesOverviewshort"  >A billionaire hired you to create a zoo with each of the major marine biomes represented. Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock the Blue Whale Hall!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesOverview"  >
         Hendrick "Pirate" Parker bought a zoo and wants you to run it! Pirate Parker is the rich and eccentric founder of the world-famous Pirate Parker's Seafood Palace restaurant chain. Not only does he run the company, he also is its flamboyantly-dressed mascot! 
         <p/>
         Pirate Parker wants you to create a zoo that teaches the public about the animal wonders of the world's oceans. To achieve this, he wants your zoo to display at least one marine species from each of the five major marine biomes: coastal, reef, pelagic, benthic, and tundra. Pirate Parker plans to pay you $10,000 for each biome represented in your zoo .
         <p/>
         Pirate Parker is famous for inspecting his holdings in person. Be on the lookout, because you never know when or where he might surface at your zoo!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesSuccess"  >Well done! Your zoo contains at least one species from each of the major marine biomes. Pirate Parker is so pleased with your progress that he gave you a special reward -- a lifetime supply of Pirate Parker's Fish Sticks!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesOverallGoal"  >Create a zoo containing at least one species from each of the major marine biomes.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesOverallGoalDone"  >You created a zoo containing species from each of the major marine biomes!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesCoastal"  >Obtain at least one species from the coastal biome and meet its basic needs to obtain a $10,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesCoastalDone"  >Well done! You have at least one species from the coastal biome on display.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesReef"  >Obtain at least one species from the reef biome and meet its basic needs to obtain a $10,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesReefDone"  >Well done! You have at least one species from the reef biome on display.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPelagic"  >Obtain at least one species from the pelagic biome and meet its basic needs to obtain a $10,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPelagicDone"  >Well done! You have at least one species from the pelagic biome on display.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesBenthic"  >Obtain at least one species from the benthic biome and meet its basic needs to obtain a $10,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesBenthicDone"  >Well done! You have at least one species from the benthic biome on display.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesTundra"  >Obtain at least one marine species from the tundra biome and meet its basic needs to obtain a $10,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesTundraDone"  >Well done! You have at least one marine species from the tundra biome on display.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateView"  >Pirate Parker, the owner of the zoo, just arrived! He says he wants to see how you're doing. He's deeply interested in all the marine animals you acquired for the zoo. In fact, Pirate Parker says that if he sees three different marine species during his visit he's rewarding you a "pirate's bounty," as he likes to put it.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateViewSuccess"  >Pirate Parker is pleased with your progress. He saw three different marine species during his visit and decided to reward you with a free animal! You can find it in a crate near the entrance of the zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateViewGoal"  >If Pirate Parker sees three different marine species in your zoo, he'll reward you.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateViewGoalDone"  >Pirate Parker saw three different marine species and gave you a reward!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateViewEntered"  >
Pirate Parker is in your zoo!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateViewFailure"  >
Pirate Parker left your zoo without seeing three marine species. You missed your chance for a reward from him.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateName"  >Pirate Parker</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateViewOneSeen"  >Pirate Parker saw one marine species.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateViewTwoSeen"  >Pirate Parker has seen two marine species. If he sees just one more, you receive a reward!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateShow"  >Pirate Parker, the owner of the zoo, has returned! On this visit, he wants to see a marine show. If Pirate Parker sees a marine show with a two-star rating or better, he says he'll "shower ye with doubloons and pieces of eight!"
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateShowSuccess"  >Pirate Parker liked your show. In fact, he liked it so much that he rewarded you with a cash grant!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateShowGoal"  >If Pirate Parker sees a marine show with a two-star rating or better, he'll reward you with a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateShowGoalDone"  >Pirate Parker saw a marine show with a two-star rating or better and rewarded you with a cash grant!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateShowEntered"  >
Pirate Parker entered your zoo!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OceansBiomesPirateShowFailure"  >
Pirate Parker left without seeing a marine show with a two-star rating or better. Sadly, you missed this opportunity for a reward.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityIntro"  >The Marine Diversity Zoo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityOverviewshort"  >Create a zoo that contains species from five major classes and orders of large marine animal. Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock the Blue Whale Hall.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityOverview"  >
         The world's oceans contain an amazing variety of animal life, ranging from microscopic zooplankton to the huge majestic whales that feed on them. Your zoo's board of directors wants to create several new exhibits that illustrate this vast diversity. Your job is to build exhibits with representatives from many different orders and classes of large marine animal.
         <p/>
         In particular, you must obtain one marine species from each of the following orders and classes:
      	<br/>
			*  A marine species from the order Carnivora (includes seals, otters, the Pacific walrus, and the polar bear)
			<br/>
			*  A species from the order Cetacea (whales and dolphins)
         <br/>
         *  A species from the class Chondrichthyes (sharks and rays)
         <br/>
         *  A species from the order Perciformes (perch-like fish)
         <br/>
         *  A marine species from the order Testudines (includes sea turtles)
         <p/>
         The zoo's board of directors decided to reward you with a cash grant of $10,000 each time you achieve one of these goals.  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversitySuccess"  >You did it! Your marine zoo contains species from a wide variety of orders and classes. Congratulations, the board of directors is extremely pleased with your work.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityOverallGoal"  >Create a zoo containing at least one marine species from each of the following orders and classes.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityOverallGoalDone"  >You created a zoo containing marine species from a variety of orders and classes!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityCarnivora"  >Obtain at least one marine species from the order Carnivora (includes seals, otters, the Pacific walrus and the polar bear) and meet its basic needs to receive a $10,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityCarnivoraDone"  >Great! You have at least one marine species from the order Carnivora on display!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityCetacea"  >Obtain at least one species from the order Cetacea (whales and dolphins) and meet its basic needs to obtain a $10,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityCetaceaDone"  >Great! You have at least one species from the order Cetacea on display!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityChondrichthyes"  >Obtain at least one species from the class Chondrichthyes (sharks and rays) and meet its basic needs to receive a $10,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityChondrichthyesDone"  >Great! You have at least one species from the class Chondrichthyes on display!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityPerciformes"  >Obtain at least one species from the order Perciformes (perch-like fish) and meet its basic needs to receive a $10,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityPerciformesDone"  >Great! You have at least one species from the order Perciformes on display!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityTestudines"  >Obtain at least one marine species from the order Testudines (includes sea turtles) and meet its basic needs to receive a $10,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityTestudinesDone"  >Great! You have at least one marine species from the order Testudines on display.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityDonations"  >To help you create a more diverse zoo, the board of directors made you the following offer: If you earn more than $7,500 in donations to marine animals, they'll reward you with a pair of emperor penguins.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityDonationsSuccess"  >Since you earned more than $7,500 in donations to marine animals, the zoo's board rewarded you with a pair of emperor penguins! You can find them in a crate near your zoo's entrance.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityDonationsGoal"  >Earn more than $7,500 in donations to marine animals to receive a free pair of penguins.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityDonationsGoalDone"  >You earned more than $7,500 in donations to marine animals and received a free pair of penguins as a reward.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityAquariums"  >To encourage you to showcase some smaller marine animals, the board of directors has made you the following offer: Place three different types of aquariums, and they'll give your zoo a hammerhead shark at no cost to you.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityAquariumsSuccess"  >As a reward for placing three different types of aquariums, the board of directors gave you a hammerhead shark! This interesting looking shark is in a crate near your zoo's entrance.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityAquariumsOverallGoal"  >Place three different types of aquariums in your zoo to receive a free hammerhead shark.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityAquariumsOverallGoalDone"  >You placed three different types of aquariums in your zoo and received a free hammerhead shark as a reward!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityAquariumsOctopusGoal"  >Place an aquarium containing an octopus.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityAquariumsOctopusGoalDone"  >You placed an aquarium containing an octopus!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityAquariumsSeahorseGoal"  >Place an aquarium containing seahorses.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityAquariumsSeahorseGoalDone"  >You placed an aquarium containing seahorses!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityAquariumsTropicalGoal"  >Place an aquarium containing tropical fish.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:MarineDiversityAquariumsTropicalGoalDone"  >You placed an aquarium containing tropical fish!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaIntro"  >Arluq the Orca</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaOverviewShort"  >Raise an orphaned orca calf to maturity. Complete all the scenarios in this campaign to unlock the Blue Whale Hall.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaOverview"  >Sometimes while hunting prey an individual orca may strand itself on shore. Much more rare are mass strandings of orcas, where entire pods of orcas strand themselves on the beach. Scientists do not know exactly why these mass strandings occur. 
      <p/>
      Arluq, a young female, is the sole survivor rescued from a mass orca stranding in the Arctic. She is being kept at a temporary facility, while officials from the Orca Rescue and Care Association look for a permanent home for her. The association wants to place her in a well-established zoo with adequate financial resources.
      <p/>
      If you earn $10,000 in donations for her care, the association can donate Arluq to your zoo!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaBasicNeeds"  >You did such an excellent job in raising donations that the Orca Rescue and Care Association donated Arluq to your zoo! You'll find Arluq, the young orca calf, crated near the entrance to your zoo.
      <p/>
      Now, it's up to you to take care of this magnificent animal. Build an exhibit for her and take care of all her basic needs.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichment"  >Arluq seems to be adjusting well to her new exhibit. As a reward for your quick action, your zoo's board of directors awarded you a $10,000 bonus.
      <p/>
      You need to make sure Arluq doesn't get bored! Orcas are intelligent, active predators that require constant stimulation. Your next goal is to obtain three different enrichment items -- a clam bubbler, a pursuit ball, and a seal prey dummy -- to meet Arluq's stimulation needs.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaCare"  >
      You did a fine job with Arluq! The Orca Rescue and Care Association wants you to continue caring for her for the next three months. Then, one of their inspectors will assess her situation and make a recommendation for her future.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaReleaseDonations"  >
      Three months passed and an inspector from the Orca Rescue and Care Association assessed Arluq's current living environment. He's concerned that her social needs are not being met. Orcas are very social animals that do not do well in isolation. The inspector's recommendation is that you release Arluq into the wild, where she can interact with other orcas. He's confident that this is the best decision for her future health and happiness.
      <p/>
      Transporting and safely releasing a large marine animal like an orca is expensive! You need to raise $25,000 in donations for the orca before returning Arluq to the wild.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaReleaseToWild"  >
      Outstanding work! You raised more than $25,000 for Arluq's safe release. It's time now for her to return home. Release Arluq to the wild to complete the scenario.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaReleaseToWildSuccess"  >
      You returned Arluq to her home waters, far north in the Arctic. Using Arluq's vocal patterns, scientists located a pod of related orcas and were able to release her near her relatives. You could tell from her excited vocalizations and belly flops that Arluq was thrilled to be with others of her kind! She joined the pod, and they accepted her. Arluq is now living happily among them as they patrol the vast ocean.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaBreed"  >
      Three months passed and an inspector from the Orca Rescue and Care Association assessed Arluq's current living situation. He says that you did an excellent job raising Arluq in a zoo environment and that it's time to take the next step. He says that you should introduce male orcas to Arluq to breed her. When she has her calf, you complete the scenario!     
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaBreedSuccess"  >
      There's a new arrival at your zoo... Arluq is now a proud mother! You started a whole new orca community in your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaSuccessOverview"  >
      You did an excellent job raising a young orca calf to maturity and caring for her. Arluq is doing wonderfully, and it's all due to your hard work!
      <p/>
		Completing this campaign unlocked the Blue Whale Hall object! You can use it in all your future Zoo Tycoon 2: Marine Mania games.       
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaDeathFailure"  >
      Arluq survived a mass stranding for orcas, but sadly, she did not survive in your zoo. You failed the scenario.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaOverallGoal"  >Take care of Arluq, a young orca rescued after a mass stranding.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaOverallGoalDone"  >You did an excellent job taking care of Arluq!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaDonationsGoal"  >Earn $10,000 in donations for marine animals to show you are capable of hosting Arluq.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaDonationsGoalDone"  >You earned more than $10,000 in donations for marine animals!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaBasicNeedsGoal"  >Meet Arluq's basic needs.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaBasicNeedsGoalDone"  >You met Arluq's basic needs!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichmentGoal"  >Buy enrichment items for Arluq and make sure her stimulation need is met.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichmentGoalDone"  >You obtained enrichment items and met Arluq's stimulation need!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichmentBubbleGoal"  >Obtain a clam bubbler enrichment item.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichmentBubbleGoalDone"  >You obtained a clam bubbler enrichment item!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichmentDummyGoal"  >Obtain a seal-shaped prey dummy enrichment item.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichmentDummyGoalDone"  >You obtained a seal prey dummy!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichmentBallGoal"  >Obtain a pursuit ball enrichment item.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichmentBallGoalDone"  >You obtained a pursuit ball!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichmentStimulationGoal"  >Meet Arluq's stimulation need.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaEnrichmentStimulationGoalDone"  >You met Arluq's stimulation need!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaCareGoal"  >Take care of Arluq for three more months. Then, an inspector is going to evaluate her living situation and make a recommendation for her future.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaCareGoalDone"  >You took care of Arluq for three additional months.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaReleaseDonationsGoal"  >Earn a grant total of $25,000 in donations for the orca, Arluq, so you can release her into the wild.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaReleaseDonationsGoalDone"  >You earned more than $25,000 in donations for the orca!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaReleaseToWildGoal"  >Release Arluq into the wild.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaReleaseToWildGoalDone"  >You released Arluq into the wild!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaBreedGoal"  >Breed Arluq with a male orca.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaBreedGoalDone"  >Arluq had a baby orca!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimals:OrcaAnimalName"  >Arluq</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimalsLabels:MarineAnimalsCampaignshort"  >Marine Animals</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimalsLabels:MarineAnimalsCampaignS1"  >Take the Plunge</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimalsLabels:MarineAnimalsCampaignS1short"  >Take the Plunge</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimalsLabels:MarineAnimalsCampaignS2"  >The Oceans' Biomes</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimalsLabels:MarineAnimalsCampaignS2short"  >Oceans' Biomes</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimalsLabels:MarineAnimalsCampaignS3"  >The Marine Diversity Zoo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimalsLabels:MarineAnimalsCampaignS3short"  >Marine Diversity Zoo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimalsLabels:MarineAnimalsCampaignS4"  >Arluq the Orca</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="MarineAnimalsLabels:MarineAnimalsCampaignS4short"  >Arluq the Orca</LOC_STRING>
   
</ZT2Strings>
